Harsh kumar Sharma

Junior Accountant

Motivated and detail-oriented junior accountant with 2 years general accounting experience. I am looking for a workplace where I can showcase my skills, use my abilities and upgrade the standards. I am keen to learn, open to feedback, adaptive to changes, practice diligence and believe in integrity.





harshsharma26281@gmai.com



9199019907



Bhagalpur, India



29 December, 1998

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR ACCOUNTANT SCI INDIA LTD.

08/2020 - Present

Bhagalpur

Work Description/Tasks

- Purchase & Sale Invoice entry
- Cash and Bank entry with reconcile bank statement and general ledger & post journal entries for accrued expenses and revenue
- Maintain and record fixed assets & assist with the preparation of financial statement
- Prepare local compliance reports & present as liaison vendor to reconcile any billing discrepancies

Paid-up Article Assistant

Sumanta & Co.

04/2019 - 03/2020 Kolkata

Work Description/Tasks

- Voucher Entry
- Sales Entries Reconcile
- Bank Statement Entry
- Cash Book Entry
- Party Purchase Reconciliation

EDUCATION

Graduation (Bachelor of Commerce)

T.M Bhagalpur University

2015 - 2019 Bhagalpur

Board

Bhagalpur University

Intermediate

Marwari College

2013 - 2015 Bhagalpur

Board

Accounts (BSEB-PATNA)

High School

Anandram Dhandaniya Sarasvati Vidya Mandir

Bhagalpur

Board

CBSE (NEW DELHI)

SKILLS AND STRENGTHS

Organized Team Work Resilience and Adaptability Time Management Quick Learner Eye for Detail Numerical skill Sharp Interpersonal skills Computer skill

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tally

Microsoft Excel - Word - Powerpoint

GST - GSTR-1, 2 & 3

CERTIFICATES

Kaushal Yuva Program (K.Y.P)

This program is held by Bihar Government to provide basics Computer Skills. The course duration for this training was 3 months.

Pradhan Mantri Kaushal Vikash Yojana (P.M.K.V.Y)

The training was held by Central Government on the subject "Logistics". The tenuity of this program was 3 months.

Startup India by Upgrad (National invest program agency) (05/2020)

This certification program was conducted by Upgrad during the lockdown 2020. This program was structured to up-skill the members on the understanding to "start your own business" and growth factors.

Career Edge- Knock down the lockdown by TCSION (04/2020 - 05/2020)

This course was designed to enhance and up level Communication Skills, Soft Skills, Business Etiquette, and other interpersonal skills by TCS.

LANGUAGES

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Marwadi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Listening Music

Playing Indoor Games

Reading

Networking

Performing Arts

Long Rides